(FUNKY R&B MUSIC)
♪ YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT ♪
♪ I LIKE THE PLAYETTES ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY, NO DOUBT ♪
♪ PLAY ON, PLAYETTE ♪
♪ YO, DRE, DROP THE VERSE ♪
♪ IT'S GOING DOWN,
FADE TO BLACKSTREET ♪
♪ THE HOMIES GOT AT ME,
COLLAB' CREATIONS,
BUMP LIKE ACNE ♪
♪ NO DOUBT, I PUT IT
DOWN, NEVER SLOUCH ♪
♪ AS LONG AS MY
CREDIT CAN VOUCH ♪
♪ A DOG COULDN'T CATCH ME OUT ♪
♪ TELL ME WHO CAN STOP
WHEN DRE MAKIN' MOVES ♪
♪ ATTRACTING HONEYS
LIKE A MAGNET ♪
♪ GIVING 'EM EARGASMS
WITH MY MELLOW ACCENT ♪
♪ STILL MOVING THIS FLAVOR ♪
♪ WITH THE HOMIES
BLACKSTREET AND TEDDY ♪
♪ THE ORIGINAL RUMP SHAKERS ♪
♪ SHORTY, GET DOWN, GOOD LORD ♪
♪ BABY GOT 'EM OPEN
ALL OVER TOWN ♪
♪ STRICTLY BIZ,
SHE DON'T PLAY AROUND ♪
♪ COVER MUCH GROUND,
GOT GAME BY THE POUND ♪
♪ GETTING PAID IS HER FORTE ♪
♪ EACH AND EVERY DAY,
TRUE PLAYER WAY ♪
♪ I CAN'T GET HER
OUT OF MY MIND, WOW ♪
♪ I THINK ABOUT THE GIRL
ALL THE TIME, WOW WOW ♪
♪ EAST SIDE TO THE WEST SIDE ♪
♪ PUSHIN' PHAT RIDES,
IT'S NO SURPRISE ♪
♪ SHE GOT TRICKS IN THE STASH,
STACKING UP THE CASH ♪
♪ FAST WHEN IT
COMES TO THE GAS ♪
♪ BY NO MEANS AVERAGE ♪
♪ SHE'S ON WHEN SHE'S
GOT TO HAVE IT ♪
♪ BABY, YOU'RE A PERFECT
10, I WANNA GET IN ♪
♪ CAN I GET DOWN SO I CAN WIN ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY,
I GOT TO BAG IT UP, BAG IT UP ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY,
I GOT TO BAG IT UP,
BAG IT UP, GIRL ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY,
I GOT TO BAG IT UP, BAG IT UP ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY,
I GOT TO BAG IT UP, GET UP ♪
♪ SHE'S GOT CLASS AND STYLE ♪
♪ STREET KNOWLEDGE
BY THE POUND ♪
♪ BABY NEVER ACT WILD,
VERY LOW KEY ON THE PROFILE ♪
♪ CATCHIN' FEELINGS IS A NO ♪
♪ LET ME TELL YOU HOW IT GOES ♪
♪ HERB'S THE WORD,
SPIN'S THE VERB ♪
♪ LOVERS IT CURVES SO
FREAK WHAT YOU HEARD ♪
♪ OH, ROLLIN' WITH
THE PHATNESS ♪
♪ YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THE HALF IS ♪
♪ YOU GOT TO PAY TO PLAY ♪
♪ JUST FOR SHORTY BANG
BANG TO LOOK YOUR WAY ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ TRUMP TIGHT ALL DAY,
EVERY DAY ♪
♪ YOU'RE BLOWING MY MIND,
MAYBE IN TIME ♪
♪ BABY, I CAN GET
YOU IN MY RIDE ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY,
I GOT TO BAG IT UP, BAG IT UP ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY,
I GOT TO BAG IT UP ♪
♪ OH YEAH ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY,
I GOT TO BAG IT UP,
BAG IT UP, BABE ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY,
I GOT TO BAG IT UP, GET UP ♪
♪ HEY YO, HEY YO,
HEY YO, HEY YO ♪
♪ HEY YO, THAT GIRL LOOKS GOOD ♪
♪ HEY YO, HEY YO,
HEY YO, HEY YO ♪
♪ PLAY ON, PLAY ON, PLAY ON ♪
♪ HEY YO, HEY YO,
HEY YO, HEY YO ♪
♪ YOU'RE MY KIND OF GIRL ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY ♪
♪ HEY YO, HEY YO,
HEY YO, HEY YO ♪
♪ HEY YO ♪
♪ 'CAUSE THAT'S MY PEEPS
AND WE ROLLS DEEP ♪
♪ FLYIN' FIRST CLASS FROM NEW
YORK CITY TO BLACKSTREET ♪
♪ WHAT YOU KNOW ABOUT
ME, NOT A THING ♪
♪ CARTIER WOODEN FRAMES
SPORTED BY MY SHORTY ♪
♪ AS FOR ME, ICY GLEAMING
PINKIE DIAMOND RING ♪
♪ WE BES THE BADDEST
CLIQUE UP ON THIS SCENE ♪
♪ AIN'T YOU GETTING BORED
WITH THESE FAKE BROADS ♪
♪ I SHOWS AND PROVES, NO
DOUBT, I BEEN DIGGIN' YOU SO ♪
♪ PLEASE EXCUSE, IF I COME
ACROSS RUDE, THAT'S JUST ME ♪
♪ AND THAT'S HOW THE
PLAYETTE'S GOT TO BE ♪
♪ STAY KICKIN' GAME
WITH A CAPITAL G ♪
♪ ASK THE PEOPLES ON MY
BLOCK, I'M AS REAL AS CAN BE ♪
♪ WORD IS BOND, FAKING
MOVES NEVER BEEN MY THING ♪
♪ SO, TEDDY, PASS THE
WORD TO YOUR CHAUNCY ♪
♪ I BE SENDING THE CALL,
LET'S SAY AROUND 3:30 ♪
♪ QUEEN PEN AND BLACKSTREET ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY, NO DOUBT BABY ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY, I
GOT TO BAG IT UP ♪
♪ GIRL, YOU GOT IT GOING ON ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY, I
GOT TO BAG IT UP ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY, I
GOT TO BAG IT UP ♪
♪ I LIKE THE WAY YOU WORK IT ♪
♪ NO DIGGITY ♪
♪ I GOT TO BAG IT UP ♪
♪ HELL YEAH, BABY ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ BLACKSTREET PRODUCTIONS ♪
♪ WE OUT, WE OUT RIGHT ♪
♪ WE OUT, WE OUT ♪